请大家注意了 好吗
May I have your attention, please?
维加斯到萨克拉门托的5 -11 -54
Five-11-54 from Vegas to Sacramento
正在离开
is now departing.
我会把这烂摊子抛在脑后
♪ I'll leave this mess behind ♪
我又要开始了
♪ I'm starting up again ♪
今晚
♪ Tonight ♪
哦 哦 哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
我要跳上失控的火车
♪ I'm jumping on the runaway train ♪
爸爸 对不起我跑了
Dad, sorry I ran off.
我需要一个新的开始
I need a fresh start.
我又要开始了
♪ I'm starting up again ♪
我受够保释你了
I'm done bailing you out.
看着对手的眼睛 即使你在洗牌
Look your opponent in the eyes, even when you're shuffling.
我不想再玩扑克了
I'm not gonna play poker anymore.
我一直想上大学
I've always wanted to go to college
我刚被第二学期录取了
and I've just been accepted second semester.
我想和同龄的孩子过正常的生活
I wanna live a normal life with kids my age.
等我准备好了再打给你
I'll call you when I'm ready to talk.
艾比
Abby.
我要一直走下去
♪ I'm going all the way ♪
我又要开始了
♪ I am starting up again ♪
嘿 朋友
Hey, pal!
嗨
Hi.
我想你了
I missed you.
我很想你
I missed you so much.
我还是不敢相信你终于来了
Still, I can't believe you're finally here.
你 我很抱歉
You, um, I'm sorry.
你穿的是什么
What are you wearing?
这是一个全新的我
It's the new me.
你好吗
You good?
是的
Yeah.
你想看看我们的宿舍吗
Do you wanna see our dorm?
是的
Yes.
因为我们是室友
Because we're roommates.
是的 -是的 太棒了
Yeah. - Yes, it's so awesome.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
见到你真高兴
It is so good to see you.
我感觉已经好几个月没见了
I feel like it's been like months.
是的 邻居都很不错
Yeah, the neighbors are pretty decent.
不过 对门的那个家伙却抽起了烟
Though, the guy across the hall vapes
那可怕的蓝莓全天候供应
that horrendous blueberry shit 24/7
还不间断地演奏五分钱乐队的歌
and also plays Nickelback nonstop.
疯了 -是的
Crazy. - Yeah.
而且 淋浴很糟糕
Also, the showers suck.
我相信淋浴不会很糟糕
I'm sure the showers don't suck.
你把这地方收拾得很整洁
So you really spruced up the place.
是的
Yeah.
你知道吗 我只是想等你回来
You know, I just wanted to wait for you to get here.
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
Shepley
Shepley.
他太性感了
And he is so hot.
嗯
Hm.
他脸上没有穿孔
He doesn't have any face piercings.
是啊 有时候你突然有一天醒来
Yeah, well, sometimes you just wake up one day
就像开心果
and like pistachios.
不过他很高兴见到你
He's really excited to meet you though
他今晚要带我们出去
and he is taking us out tonight.
哦 不 梅 我太累了
Oh no, Mer, I'm so tired.
不
No.
我刚到这里 坐了很长的车
I just got here, it was a long bus ride.
我只想待在这里学习
I just wanna stay here and study.
会很冷的
It'll be so chill.
天主教学校会放你一晚假
Catholic school will let you off for one night.
来吧 -不 我不去
Come on. - No, I'm not going.
是的 我们要去
Yes, we're going.
取下贞操带
Take off the chastity belt
我们走吧 -不 我不想去
and let's go. - No, I don't wanna go.
我必须学习
I have to study,
Mer Mer
Mer, Mer!
我们要去哪里
So where are we going?
哦 真是个惊喜
Oh, it's a surprise.
我想有个人
I think there's a guy...
不要紧
never mind.
对了 顺便说一下 我们不讨论圆
Oh, hey, oh, by the way, we don't talk about the circle.
这是个秘密
It's a secret.
什么是秘密
What's a secret?
完全正确
Exactly.
欢迎来到大屠杀
Welcome to the bloodbath!
哇
Whoo!
如果你在找经济学101
If you're looking for Economics 101,
你来错地方了
you are in the wrong fucking place,
但如果你寻找圆圈 这里就是麦加
but if you seek the circle, this is Mecca.
我叫亚当
My name is Adam.
规则由我定 比赛由我定
I make the rules and I call the fight.
今晚 我们迎来了新的挑战者
Tonight, we have a new challenger,
东部明星大学摔跤手马立克·杨
Eastern star varsity wrestler Marek Young.
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
现在 卫冕冠军无需介绍
Now, reigning champ needs no introduction,
但因为他吓死我了
but because he scares the shit out of me,
我要给他一个
I'm gonna give him one.
所以赶紧抖抖靴子 小伙子们 脱下内裤 女士们
So shake in your boots, boys, and drop your panties, ladies.
有请特拉维斯"疯狗"马多克斯
I give you Travis "Mad Dog" Maddox!
哇
Whoo!
你知道 这不是为我准备的
You know, this isn't for me.
我要回宿舍学习了
I'm gonna go back to the dorm and study.
你好
Hello.
我可以吗
May I?
啊哈
Uh-huh.
崔维斯 崔维斯 崔维斯 崔维斯
Travis, Travis, Travis, Travis.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
战斗
Fight!
是啊
Yeah!
哦 好的
Oh, okay.
哦 狗屎
Oh, shit!
加油 特拉维斯
Come on, Travis!
钱 甜蜜的钱
Money, sweet money.
呃 打扰一下
Um, excuse me.
你是新来的吗
Are you new here?
是的 我
Yeah, I.
哇
Whoa!
哦 狗屎
Oh, shit!
起来 崔维斯 快点 -起来
Get up, Travis, come on! - Get up!
快点 起来 -起来
Come on, get up! - Get up!
是啊
Yeah!
两个
Two-one.
别这样 特拉维斯
Come on, Travis.
赢家
Winner!
特拉维斯
Travis!
你没事吧
You okay?
啊哈
Uh-huh.
嘿 你站在这儿
Hey, you standing here.
我不知道这对我是否有好处
I don't know if that's good for me.
我通常不会那样分心的
I usually don't get distracted like that.
抱歉弄丢了你的毛衣 鸽子
Sorry about your sweater, pigeon.
Whoa -ha
Whoa-ha.
嗯
Grr.
崔维斯 你是我的摇钱树 宝贝
Travis, you are my cash cow, baby.
我不能带你去任何地方
I can't take you anywhere.
我想知道你认为我是谁
♪ I'd like to know who you think I am ♪
我不是你的女人 你也不是我的男人
♪ I'm not your woman, you're not my man ♪
你会把河分开 然后你会建造水坝
♪ You'll part the river and then you'll build the dam ♪
所以不要扮演受害者
♪ So don't play the victim ♪
因为一切都在你的手中 你的手中
♪ 'Cause it was all in your hands, your hands ♪
一切都在你的手中 你的手中
♪ It was all in your hands, your hands ♪
怎么了 鸽子
What's up, pigeon?
我他妈的恨你
I fucking hate you!
放松点
Relax!
你昨晚没回家
You didn't come home last night.
你是个骗子
You're a liar.
冷静下来
Calm down.
你是个骗子
You're a liar.
哇
Wow.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
听着 艾比
Listen, Abby,
需要支付学费
tuition payments need to be issued
通过银行账户或信用卡
through a bank account or a credit card.
要考虑问责制
There is accountability to be considered,
更不用说税收了
not to mention the taxes.
我正在办一个
I'm in the process of setting one up.
你父母不能帮帮你吗
Can't your parents help you out?
它是复杂的
It's complicated.
我妈妈 我已经很多年没联系了
My mom, I haven't spoken to in years,
我爸爸也不是最好的人
and my dad is not the best guy.
这学期我同意
I'll allow it for this semester,
但你得给自己开个银行账户
but sort yourself out a bank account
因为这种事不会再发生了
because this will not be happening again.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢 谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
所以我今早跟会计谈过了
So I talked to the bursar this morning
最后她拿走了钱
and she ended up taking the cash.
我是说 至少我这学期有保险
I mean, at least I'm covered for the semester.
哦 如果钱用光了怎么办
Oh, what happens when the money runs out?
我不知道
I don't know.
我要么找份工作 要么拿奖学金
I'll find a job or I'll get a scholarship.
我会想办法的
I'll figure something out.
传入的
Incoming.
嘿 南瓜
Hey, pumpkin.
我给你倒了杯咖啡
I got you a coffee here.
谢谢你 哦
Thank you. - Aw.
这是给你的
That's for you.
谢谢
Thanks.
昨晚怎么样
How was last night?
你玩得开心吗
Did you have fun?
是啊 很难忘
Yeah, it was memorable.
那一个人到底是怎么回事
So what was the deal with the one guy,
那个浑身是纹身的人
the guy that was covered in tattoos?
哦 那是他的表弟
Oh, that's his cousin.
他是大二学生
He's a sophomore.
哦 那家伙上过大学
Oh, that guy goes to college?
嗯嗯
Mm-hm.
哇 真让人吃惊
Wow, that is surprising.
令人惊讶的是什么
What's surprising?
你去上大学
That you go to college.
为什么我不能上大学
Why can't I go to college?
不是我说的 兄弟 是她说的
I didn't say it, bro, she said it.
怎么啦
What?
不 我没那么说
No, I didn't say that.
对不起 我们见过面吗
Sorry, have we met?
你不记得了 崔维斯
Oh, you don't remember, Travis?
你 你毁了她的毛衣
You, you ruined her sweater.
我毁了很多毛衣
I ruin a lot of sweaters.
我很确定他们用了不好的双关语
I'm pretty sure they retired bad double entendres.
鸽子
Pigeon.
艾比
Abby.
我叫艾比
My name is Abby.
特拉维斯
Travis.
特拉维斯马多克斯
Travis Maddox.
这个动作真的有效吗
Does that move really work?
不 一次都没有
No, not a single time,
但它是真诚的
but it is sincere.
你不是我喜欢的类型
You're not my type.
每个人都喜欢我
I'm everybody's type.
看 我抓到你了
See, I got you.
我得到了你的微笑
I got a smile out of you.
不 不 那不是笑
No, no, that was not a smile.
那其实是一种居高临下的窃笑
That was actually a condescending chuckle.
是的
Yeah.
嘿 我要过去了 好吗
Hey, I'm gonna come over, all right?
再见 鸽子
See you later, pigeon.
艾比 我叫艾比
Abby, my name is Abby.
现在是鸽子了
Well, it's pigeon now.
你能相信那个家伙吗
Can you believe that guy?
这就是带给我们的
And that is what brings us
对博弈论的发现
to the discovery of game theory.
博弈论是20世纪50年代首创的一个术语
Now, game theory is a term that was pioneered in the 1950s
由数学家约翰·纳什提出
by mathematician John Nash.
游戏一词被定义为任何互动
The term game is defined as any interaction
每个人的收益在哪里
where each person's payoff
受到决策的影响 毫米
is affected by the decisions. - Mm.
哇
Wow.
这么热
So hot.
那是我的最爱
That one's my favorite.
现在关闭已经太晚了
It's too late to close it now.
有没有人告诉过你 这是不礼貌的
Has anyone ever told you that it's not very polite...
年轻的女士吗
Young lady?
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
艾比
Abby.
艾比女士 你能教我们一下吗
Ms. Abby, would you care to educate us
为什么纳什均衡与博弈论无关
as to why Nash's equilibrium is irrelevant to game theory?
无关紧要的
Irrelevant?
我不能
I can't.
好吧 那也许你应该多关注一下
Well, then perhaps you should focus a little more on...
但那是因为它是相关的
Well, but that's because it is relevant.
如果达到平衡
If equilibrium is achieved,
这意味着双方玩家都无法提高收益
that means that both players can't increase payoff
通过单方面改变决定
by changing decisions unilaterally.
它也可以被称为无悔
It can also be known as no regrets
从某种意义上说 一旦玩家做出决定
in the sense that once a player does make a decision,
考虑到后果 他们不会后悔
they'll have no regrets thinking about the consequences.
你有提前阅读吗
Have you been reading ahead?
一点
A bit.
就像我说的
As I was saying.
哇 鸽子 太辣了
Wow, pigeon, that was so hot.
你有脑子
You got brains.
你为什么在这里
Why are you here?
你为什么要给我一个模棱两可的信号
Why are you sending me a mixed signal?
我的信号并没有混淆
There's nothing mixed about my signals.
我刚发现你在ins上跟踪我
I just caught you Insta stalking me.
我没有在ins上跟踪
I was not Insta stalking.
听着 我可以帮你省下不少时间
Look, I'm going to save you a lot of wasted time.
你别再胡闹了 好吗
You can stop the antics, okay?
我不会和你上床的
I'm not sleeping with you.
我不是想和你上床 也不是想装你
I'm not trying to sleep with you or bag you.
我只是想请你吃饭
I'm just trying to take you to dinner.
包我
Bag me?
我是什么 杂货吗
What am I, groceries?
你在过去的四年里没看过报纸吗
Have you not read a newspaper in the last four years?
男人不再那样说话了
Men don't talk like that anymore.
哪个男人
Which men?
地球上进化的人类
The evolved men of planet Earth.
那些真正了解自己感受的人
The ones who are actually in touch with their feelings.
我不喜欢你
I don't like you.
别烦我
Leave me alone.
你不会就此罢休的 对吧
You're not going to let this go, aren't you?
我八点钟来接你
I'll pick you up at eight.
等等 你没有我的号码
But wait, you don't have my number.
兴趣发挥他的作用
Interest to play his part.
你为我盛装打扮
You dress up for me?
不 我没必要 因为这不是约会
No, I didn't have to because this is not a date.
我希望你饿了
Well, I hope you're hungry.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
我不需要这个 因为我不上那个东西
I don't need this because I'm not getting on that thing.
是的 你是
Yeah, you are.
你知道摩托车事故的统计数字吗
Do you know the statistics of motorcycles in accidents?
不 我才不穿那玩意
No, I'm not putting on that thing.
是的 你是
Yeah, you are.
我可以整晚都这样
I can do this all night.
很好
Fine.
谢谢 米格尔 是的
Thanks, Miguel. - Yep.
你真的不让我请你吃饭吗
You're really not gonna let me buy you dinner?
不 这不是约会
No, this isn't a date.
是的 我知道
Yes, I'm aware.
你已经说了两次了
You've said that twice now.
哦 你注意到了
Oh, you noticed.
嗯嗯
Mm-hm.
还有你的衣服
That and your outfit,
上面写着"我讨厌特拉维斯"
which screams "I detest Travis."
我不讨厌你
I don't detest you.
我只是不喜欢定局
I just don't like being a foregone conclusion
你床柱上无数无数的凹痕中的一个
for one of the many, many, many notches on your bedpost.
哦 你真聪明
Oh, you're smart.
我喜欢这样
I like that.
这可能是你不习惯在女人身上看到的
Something you're probably not used to in a woman.
哦 我三振出局了
Oh, I'm striking out.
我投降
I surrender.
我们至少可以做朋友
We can at least be friends.
朋友 但没有好处
Friends, but with no benefits.
我们没有睡在一起
We're not sleeping together.
我都不会去想什么好处
I won't even think about the benefits
除非你希望我这么做
unless you want me to.
不 这样我们才能继续做朋友
No, that can't happen so that we can stay friends.
朋友
Friends.
我来这里好几年了
I've been coming to this place for years.
我家离那儿只有三英里
My family home is only three miles that way.
哦
Aw.
你就不能离你妈妈远一点吗
You couldn't move farther away from your mommy?
不 不是这样的
No, that's not it.
她的烤奶酪就这么好吃
Her grilled cheese was just that good?
好吧 她死了
Well, she's dead.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
我真是个混蛋 我很抱歉
I'm such an asshole, I'm so sorry.
我感觉糟透了 -没事的 没事的
I feel horrible. - It's okay, it's okay.
那时我只有三岁
I was only three.
好吧 我没那么抱歉
Okay, I'm not that sorry.
别碰我
Get your hand off me.
你爸爸怎么样了
How's your dad?
他还活着 所以你可以取笑他
He's still alive, so you can make fun of him.
他是个好人
He's a good man.
他一个人养大了五个儿子
He raised five boys all on his own.
马多克斯五兄弟
Five Maddox brothers?
是的
Yeah.
托马斯 泰勒 泰勒 特伦特和特拉维斯
Thomas, Taylor, Tyler, Trent, and Travis.
如果你想擅长打架
If you wanna get good at fighting,
四个哥哥每天都打你的屁股
having four older brothers beat your ass daily
是一个很好的开始
is a good place to start.
但为什么要这么做呢
But why do it?
上大学可不便宜
College ain't cheap.
打架是赚钱的好方法
Fighting is a good way to make money.
似乎没有必要冒险
Just seems unnecessarily risky.
为什么
Why?
你担心我
You worried about me?
一点也不
Not even in the slightest.
你的故事是什么
What's your story?
只是一个普通小镇里的普通女孩
Just your average girl from your ordinary town.
哦 爸爸妈妈
Oh, mom and dad?
每个都有一个
One of each.
哇 你的信息真丰富
Wow, you're a wealth of information.
我不可能一夜之间把所有的东西都送出去
Well, I can't give away all the goods in one night.
大多数人都喜欢这么做
Most do.
我其实很喜欢
I actually enjoy it.
你真的要走吗
Are you seriously leaving?
晚餐结束
Dinner's over.
我们才刚刚开始
We just got started.
晚安 特拉维斯
Good night, Travis.
嘿 紫色毛衣
Hey, purple sweater.
什么帮助 -是的
Little help? - Yeah.
噢
Ooh!
哦 不
Oh, no!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
警察
Police.
他 他很好
He's, he's fine.
好吧 没事的
Okay, it's okay.
他是好的
He's okay.
我很好
I'm fine.
好吧 你没事吧
Okay, are you okay?
哦 我没事
Oh, I'm fine.
好吧 我很抱歉
Okay, I'm so sorry.
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
哦
Oh!
你很可爱 还在哭
You're so cute and you're crying,
我发誓 -我没有 我没有哭
I swear. - I'm not, I'm not crying.
是 呃 是风
It's, uh, it's the wind.
你当飞盘俱乐部的队长多久了
How long have you been captain of the Frisbee club?
不不不 我不是队长
Oh, no, no, no, I'm not captain
飞盘俱乐部的成员 -哦 那是
of the Frisbee club. - Oh, it was, uh,
这是个玩笑
it was a joke.
开个玩笑 我没事的
It was a joke, I'll be okay.
噢 嗨 -嗨
Oh, hi. - Hi.
嗨 我是艾比
Hi, I'm Abby.
我要走了
I'm gonna go.
我 我要摇晃了
I'm, I'm gonna wobble.
你应该在蛋蛋上敷点冰
You should put some ice on your balls.
你应该在我蛋蛋上敷点冰
You should put some ice on my balls.
好吧
Okay.
是啊 我要走了
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna go.
很高兴见到你 帕克
It was really nice to meet you, Parker.
哦
Oh!
谢谢你 小伙子
Thanks, man.
去你妈的
Fuck you!
小心
Be careful!
噢
Ow!
Ow.
谁能把水打开吗
Could someone turn the water back on?
舍监说我们会缺水
So the RA said we're gonna be without water
在接下来的24小时内 所以只是今晚
for the next 24 hours, so it's just for the night.
你确定谢普利不介意吗
Are you sure Shepley is cool with this?
嘿 艾比要留下来过夜
Hey, Abby's staying over.
别进崔维斯的房间 好吗
Just stay out of Travis's room, all right?
怎么啦
What?
你没告诉我
You didn't tell me
特拉维斯住在这里 -不 我当然知道
that Travis lives here. - No, of course I did.
不 记住 我告诉过你
No, remember, I told you.
不不不不
No, no, no, no,
不 不 不 -我不要呆在这里
no, no, no. - I'm not staying here.
艾比 艾比 -不 我要走了
Abby, Abby! - No, I'm leaving.
不 我保证你永远见不到他
No, I promise you will never see him.
他都没来过这里
He's never even here.
你不会见到他的 我保证
You won't see him, I promise.
你必须留下 会很有趣的
You have to stay, It'll be so fun.
告诉她崔维斯会没事的
Hey, tell her that Travis will be okay.
他不会在乎的 他喜欢你
Oh, he won't care, he likes you.
他不认识我
He doesn't know me.
他喜欢你
He likes you.
我们要去朋友家过夜
We're gonna have a sleepover.
太有趣了 我们要做巧克力夹心饼干
So much fun, we'll make s'mores.
嘿 我们走吧
Hey, let's go.
再见
Bye.
艾比 宝贝 是爸爸
Abby, babe, it's Dad.
你去哪儿了
Where'd you go?
你能回个电话或者至少给我回个短信吗
Could you return the call or at least text me back?
妈的 妈的 妈的 妈的
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
原谅我
Excuse me.
确定
Sure.
好的 谢谢
Okay, merci.
耶稣
Jesus.
喜欢这个节目吗
Enjoy the show?
你吓死我了
You scared the crap out of me.
你知道这不是一个很有吸引力的习语
You know that's not a very attractive idiom
一旦你停下来好好想想
once you stop and think about it.
因为在你的性别歧视世界里
Because in your sexist universe,
女人实际上不排便
women don't actually defecate?
这词对你这种人来说再合适不过了
Wow, that's a perfect word for someone like you.
你知道以前的说法是"别烦我了"吗
Did you know that the saying used to be "bejesus out of me?"
你朋友让我把这个给你
Your friend gave this to me to give to you.
怎么啦
What?
就是刚刚跟你上床的那个女人
The woman that you just had sex with
给了你她的电话号码 你就这么扔掉了
gives you her number and you just throw it away?
那不是她留下的号码
That's not her leaving her number.
这是她在标记自己的领地
That's her marking her territory.
那也许你不该和她上床
Well, then maybe you shouldn't have sex with her.
我不记得答应过她什么
I don't remember promising her a thing.
哇
Wow.
你体现了你们性别的所有错误
You embody everything that is wrong with your gender.
她是个成年人了
She's an adult.
我是个成年人了
I'm an adult.
这是双方自愿的
It was consensual.
看看这个
Look at this.
同意的日期
Consent date.
现在再小心也不为过
Can never be too careful nowadays.
你和多少女人签了合同
How many women do you have contracts with?
不知道 我重质量轻数量
No idea, I'm a quality guy over quantity.
我要吐了
I'm gonna throw up.
我的卧室在走廊尽头
Well, my bedroom is down the hall
当你想睡觉的时候 床是你的
and the bed is all yours for when you wanna crash.
我才不要睡你的床
I'm not gonna sleep in your bed.
为什么
Why?
只有我睡在我的床上
No one but me sleeps in my bed.
我的床是圣地
My bed is sacred ground.
那我为什么还能睡你的床
Well, then why would I be allowed in your bed?
你今晚打算和我做爱吗
Are you planning on having sex with me tonight?
不
No.
那就这么定了
Then it's settled.
哇 别客气
Wow, make yourself at home.
抱歉 我上午10点有要紧事 死记硬背的生物考试
Sorry, I just have a big 10 a.m. Bio test to cram for,
但我可以搬回厨房
but I can move back to the kitchen.
不 你很好 待在原地
No, you're fine, stay where you're at.
别傻了
Don't be silly.
谢谢你
Thank you.
要我给你泡点茶什么的吗
Do you want me to make you some tea or something?
没有 但是我的荧光笔坏了
No, but, uh, my highlighter just died.
我能借一个吗
Can I borrow one?
对了 看看最上面的抽屉
Oh, yeah, check the top drawer.
等一下 嗯
Wait, um,
不
no.
哇
Wow.
这是很多
That's a lot.
实行安全性行为是犯罪吗
Is practicing safe sex a crime?
这是什么
What's this?
我告诉你 这不是荧光笔
It's not a highlighter, I'll tell you that.
嗯
Um.
是溜溜球
It's a yo-yo?
不 绝对不是
No, definitely not.
这是尴尬的
It's awkward.
我要去洗澡了
I'm gonna go shower.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
坏猫
Bad kitty.
鼠标
Mouse.
艾比
Abby.
鸽子 -真的很可爱
Pigeon. - Really cute.
多少钱
How much?
嗯
Um.
不是你想的那样
It's not what do you think it is.
艾比 你
Abby, you're...
等等 你在干什么
Wait, what are you doing?
艾比
Abby!
搞什么鬼
What the heck?
你怎么了
What is wrong with you?
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything.
你触动了我
You touched me.
这句话出自一个愤怒的男人之口
Oh, says the man with the raging hard-on.
你应该被关起来
You should be locked up.
你就是那个摸小鸡鸡的人
You're the sleepy cock toucher.
我没有把你的手放在那里
I didn't put your hand there.
如果你费心去读一本生物教科书
And if you bothered to read a biology textbook,
你会发现
you'd find out
这被称为副交感神经反应
that it's called parasympathetic nerve response
如果你知道什么 你就会知道
and you'd know that if you knew anything
关于生物学或男人
about biology or men.
哦 该死 生物
Oh, shit, Bio!
现在几点了
What time is it?
9:42.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你穿的是什么
What are you wearing?
我们在玩 -我们是
We were playing. - We were
玩
playing.
让我载你一程
Let me give you a ride.
不 这只是个疯人院
No, this is just a madhouse.
一个护士吗
A nurse?
是的 不 我
Yeah, no, I...
对不起 打扰一下
Sorry, excuse me.
对不起
Sorry.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我滑倒了
I slipped.
但我的生物考试还是考得很好
But I still aced my Bio test.
我很高兴你没引人注意
Well, I'm glad you're not drawing attention
对自己
to yourself.
搞笑
Hilarious.
好了 我得去上课了
Okay, I have to run to class,
但我想知道昨晚发生了什么
but I want a full play-by-play of what happened last night.
昨晚什么事也没发生
Nothing happened last night.
是吗 -我不喜欢他
Yeah? - I do not like him.
是的
Yeah,
所以你才要跟他说声早安
and that's why you're giving him a good morning handy.
米克还在烦你吗
Is Mick still bothering you?
是的
Yeah.
你得把他赶出你的生活
You got to cut him out of your life.
他从我的生活中消失了
He is out of my life.
他并没有从你的生活中消失
He is not out of your life
因为他还在给你发短信
because he is still texting you.
我得去上课了
I-I gotta go to class.
怎么啦
What?
嘿
Hey.
帕克 我们又见面了
Parker, we meet again.
艾比 你还好吗
Abby, are you okay?
是啊 说来话长
Yeah, yeah, it's a long story.
嘿 你的蛋蛋怎么样了
Hey, um, how are your, your balls?
不好的
Not good.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
没关系
That's okay.
我记得他们说我有20%的机会过正常的性生活
I think they said I had a 20% chance of a normal sex life.
你在耍我吗
Are you messing with me?
不有趣吗
Not funny?
不 这很搞笑
No, it was, it was hilarious.
好吧 再见
Well, um, okay, bye.
你今晚有晚餐计划吗
Do you have dinner plans tonight?
我吗
Me?
是的
Yes.
不 我没有晚餐安排
No, I-I-I-I do not have dinner plans.
我知道一家很棒的意大利餐厅
I know a great Italian spot.
嗯 嗯
Um, um...
这是 这是吗 -不 这是同意
Is that a, is that? - No, that is a yes.
是的 我很乐意
Yes, I would love that very much.
七点来接我 我住在塔克宿舍
Pick me up at seven, I live at Tucker dormitory.
当然 到时候我去接你
Sure, I'll pick you up then.
好吧
Okay.
再见
Bye.
我看见你了
I see you!
哦 帕克
Oh, Parker.
真的吗
Really?
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢你 帕克
Thank you, Parker.
不可能 特拉维斯·马多克斯
Oh, no way, Travis Maddox.
你可以继续敲门 但我不会开门的
You can keep knocking but I am not gonna answer that door.
不可能
No way.
回头见 帕克
I'll see you soon, Parker.
再次谢谢你 桑尼
Thanks again, Sonny.
任何时候 医生
Anytime, doctor.
医生海耶斯
Doctor Hayes.
你知道 他操之过急了
He's jumping the gun, you know.
我才刚开始 仅此而已
I just started, that's all.
哇 fancy -fancy
Wow, fancy-fancy.
是的
Yeah.
哇
Wow.
你随叫随到吗
Are you on call?
不 我只是收到今晚一场演出的通知
No, I-I just got a heads-up about a show tonight.
哦 哦 我可以自己搭车回家
Oh, oh, I can get my own ride home.
不不不 我们应该一起去
No, no, no, we-we should both go.
除非你有工作或者不想见到我
Unless you've got work or sick of seeing me.
不
No.
不 我很想去
No, I would love to go.
这会很有趣的
This is-this is gonna be fun.
知道吗 我一直想见提图斯·安多尼克斯
You know, I've always wanted to see Titus Andronicus.
它被认为是莎士比亚最暴力的戏剧
It's considered to be Shakespeare's most violent play.
你不介意暴力吗
You don't mind violence?
不 我从小就是个假小子
No, I was something of a tomboy growing up.
那你就有机会了
Well, then you're in for a treat.
哦 我想开始了
Ooh, I guess it's starting.
他是州冠军
...he's a state champ.
他会挺身而出的
He's gonna come out swinging.
他不会浪费任何时间的
He's not gonna be wasting any sort of time.
好吧 你在干什么
Okay, what are you doing?
艾比今天还没回我短信
Abby hasn't texted me back today.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你能忘了艾比吗
Would you forget about Abby?
你见过这个人吗
Have you, have you seen this guy?
他穿着白色长袍 系着一条很大的腰带
He's got a white robe and a belt that's huge, okay?
我是说 你表现得像个接吻亭
I mean, you're acting like the kissing booth over here.
你需要集中注意力
You need to focus.
我很专注
I am focused.
这才是我们需要的特拉维斯
That's the Travis we need.
来吧
Come on.
我只是不知道她为什么不回我短信
I just don't know why she hasn't texted me back.
我要出去看看
I'm gonna go outside and see
如果我的手机信号好点
if I can get better cell reception.
我们死了
We're dead.
哦 哇 现代的诠释
Oh, wow, modern interpretation.
我喜欢莎士比亚
I love Shakespeare.
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
接下来是主要节目:
Next up, we have the main event:
弗雷迪·海弗林对阵特拉维斯·"疯狗"·马多克斯
Freddy Heflin versus Travis "Mad Dog" Maddox!
这会很棒的
This is gonna be great.
特拉维斯是个十足的动物
Travis is a real animal.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
没事 没事 只是这里有点热
Yeah, yeah, it's just a little hot in here.
我去找个洗手间
I'm gonna go find a bathroom.
怎么回事 艾比
What the fuck, Abby?
你不回我一条短信
You don't respond to any of my texts,
现在你穿成这样来了
and now you're here dressed like that
你的咪咪露在外面
with your titties hanging out.
他们没有出去玩
They are not hanging out.
这是有品位的乳沟
This is a tasteful amount of cleavage.
是吗
Yeah?
他们让我分心了
Well, they're distracting me.
哦 对不起 我忘了
Oh, I'm sorry, I forgot.
都是为了你 你这个自大狂
It's all about you, you egomaniac.
我必须打败你
I must break you.
大胆去做吧
Go for it.
这就是你的对手
That's who you're fighting?
是的
Yes.
那家伙会杀了你的
That guy could kill you.
这是你承认你喜欢我的奇怪方式吗
Is this your weird little way of admitting you like me?
我不喜欢你
I don't like you.
但我确实担心你
But I do worry about you.
我担心地球
I worry about the planet.
这是两种完全不同的东西
They're two very different things.
好吧 如果这样能让你放心
Okay, well, if it puts your mind at ease,
他甚至不会打我
he's not even gonna hit me.
搞笑
Hilarious.
你在怀疑我吗
Are you doubting me?
是的
Yeah.
想让它有趣点吗
Care to make it interesting?
让它变得有趣
Make it interesting?
比如打赌
Like a bet?
是的
Yeah.
我不敢打赌
I don't bet.
快点 崔维斯 他们需要你
Come on, Travis, they need you.
好的 等一下
Yeah, just a minute.
这是如何
How's this?
如果他敢碰我一下
If he manages to lay a hand on me,
我一个星期不做爱
I'll go without sex for a week.
哦
Ooh.
一个月
A month.
三个月
Three months.
三个月吗
Three months?
这对你这样的人来说是不可能的
That's impossible for someone like you.
好吧 如果我赢了 你得跟我住一个月
Okay, and if I win, you have to stay with me for a month.
你在
You're on.
但如果你想清楚
But get it through your head,
我永远不会和你做爱
I am never having sex with you.
我不想和你做爱 小猪猪
I don't wanna have sex with you, pidge.
我想在你身边
I wanna be around you.
你对我有好处
You're good for me.
你很帅
You are handsome.
你死了
You're dead.
哈
Hah.
你帅得要命
You are handsome as hell.
难怪你是冠军
No wonder you're the champ.
我心中的冠军
Champ of my heart.
来吧 打他
Come on, hit him!
你去过断背山吗
You ever hiked Brokeback Mountain?
你想要吗
Do you wanna?
我会很温柔的 你知道的
I'll be gentle, you know.
你要怎么杀了我 大男孩
How are you gonna kill me, big boy?
头晕了
Giddy up.
杀了你
...kill you!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
闭嘴
Shut up.
揍他
Hit him!
只有一次
Just once!
哦哦 宝贝摔倒了
Oh-oh, baby fell down.
回到你的婴儿床里去 小宝贝
Get back in your crib, little baby.
Oh -ho -ho
Oh-ho-ho.
现在 这个一定很疼
Now, that one had to hurt.
所以我把左上角放袜子的抽屉留给你
So I'm saving the upper left sock drawer for you.
跟我打吧 贱人
Fight me, bitch.
然后把它们盖起来
And cover those up.
你婊子
You bitch.
原谅我
Excuse me.
就一次 打他
Just once, hit him!
我们开始吧
Here we go!
女士们先生们 有请特拉维斯·马多克斯
Ladies and gentlemen, Travis Maddox!
收拾你的行李 鸽子
Pack your bags, pigeon.
你和我一起回家
You're coming home with me.
这是怎么发生的
How did this happen?
嘿 我给你拿了杯水
Hey, I got you a water.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
我只是需要消化一下
I just need to process this.
我知道
I know.
我们出去吃了一顿丰盛的晚餐
We go out for a great dinner.
相处得很好
Get on really well.
我带你去看表演
I take you to a show.
我离开你五分钟
I leave you for five minutes.
在那段时间里
And during that time,
你决定搬去和特拉维斯·马多克斯住了
you've decided to move in with Travis Maddox.
我打赌输了
I lost a bet.
正确的
Right.
我们只是朋友
We're just friends.
我是说 我们连朋友都算不上
I mean, we're not even friends.
我们什么都没有
We're nothing.
今晚和你在一起很开心
I had a really nice time with you tonight
我很乐意再来一次
and I would love to do it again.
你觉得我能得到一个晚安吻吗
Do you think I can, I can get a good-night kiss?
哦 上帝
Oh, God!
不
No!
特拉维斯
Travis!
该走了
Time to go.
是啊 你得 你得下车
Yeah, you need to, you need to leave the car.
他什么都不会做
He is not going to do anything.
看到了吗
See?
不 他会伤害我的 -他不会伤害你的
No, he's gonna hurt me. - He's not gonna hurt you.
不 他会伤害我的
No, he's gonna hurt me.
打开门
Open the door.
从车里出来 没有
Get out of the car. - No.
请下车
Please get out the car!
你很坚强 没关系
You are strong, it's okay.
不 他是个疯子
No, he is a maniac.
他会伤害我的
He is gonna hurt me,
下车 -他不会伤害你的
leave the car! - He's not going to hurt you.
马上下车 -我的天啊
Leave the car now! - Oh, my God.
从他妈的车里出来
Get out the fucking car!
开门 -你疯了
Open the door! - You're being insane.
好吧 好吧 -下车
Okay, okay. - Leave the car.
快 快 下车 -好吧 我走了
Go, go, leave the car! - Okay, I'm leaving.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
请去
Go, please.
走了
Go now.
好吧
Okay.
哦 耶稣
Oh, Jesus.
好的 这就去
Yeah, on it, yeah.
我不敢相信这一切发生了
I cannot believe this is happening.
我郑重声明
Well, for the record,
我以为你不会真的结清
I didn't think you'd really settle up.
我打赌了 但我输了
Well, I made a bet, I lost.
你说到做到
You're only as good as your word.
我熬过了一个晚上 没有发生任何奇怪的事情
I made it through one night without any funny business.
我想我还能撑过30个
I think I can make it through 30 more.
怎么啦
What?
你确实给了我一个
Well, you did give me a...
我没有给你方便
I did not give you a handy.
我再也没兴趣摸你的鸡巴了
I have no interest in touching your dick ever again.
哦 哦 -好的 明白了吗
Oh, oh. - Okay, got it?
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
你有点暴躁了
You're getting a little aggro.
哦 什么
Oh, what?
有感情的女人会让你害怕吗
Do women with emotions make you scared?
嗯
Uh-uh.
等我来例假再说吧 好吗
You wait till I'm on my period, okay?
我可能会刺伤你
I might stab you.
抱歉 我以为这是个有趣的主意
Sorry, I thought this would be a fun idea.
好吧 它不是
Well, it wasn't.
不如我们去睡觉吧
How about we just go to sleep?
你觉得呢
Yeah, you think?
给我这个 我要那个
Give me this, I want that.
别碰我
And don't touch me!
别越界 好吗
Don't cross this line, okay?
长城
Wall of China.
我从未想过我会如此想念你
♪ I never thought I'd miss you half this much ♪
我刚打扫过这里
I just cleaned in here.
你们活得像动物一样
You live like animals.
你们太脏了
You guys are filthy.
艾比 别这样
Abby, come on.
别挡道
Get out of the way.
快点 别挡道
Come on, get out of the way.
艾比 让开
Abby, get out of the way!
嘿
Hey!
不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no!
关于你
♪ About you ♪
加油 姑娘们
Come on, girls.
只要我醒来
♪ As soon as I wake up ♪
任何一个夜晚你介意吗
♪ Any night ♪ - Do you mind?
任何一天
♪ Any day ♪
我知道我需要你带走我的忧郁
♪ I know that it's you I need to take the blues away ♪
那一定是爱
♪ It must be love ♪
爱 爱
♪ Love, love ♪
一定是爱吧 -闭嘴
♪ It must be love ♪ - Shut up.
爱 爱
♪ Love, love ♪
哦
Oh.
没什么了
♪ Nothing more ♪
什么都没有
♪ Nothing less ♪
爱是最好的
♪ Love is the best ♪
我们怎么能说这么多
♪ How can it be that we can say so much ♪
谢普 我要去趟商店
Hey, Shep, I'm gonna hit the store.
你想要吗
Do you want?
把它拿出来 没错
Bring it up, yeah.
是的
Yeah.
祝福你 祝福我 宝贝
♪ Bless you and bless me, baby ♪
我在努力 我在努力 -上 上 上 上
I'm trying, I'm trying! - Up, up, up, up.
好了 干得好 回家吧
Okay, good job, go home.
你要辞职吗
Are you gonna quit?
接着说 -不 我在努力
Go on then! - No, I'm trying!
我尝试
I'm trying!
是的
Yup.
一个
One.
两个
Two.
你知道 这真的很简单
You know, this is really easy.
你让这一切变得如此艰难
You made this so hard.
哦
Oh.
不 我能行
No, I can do it.
我不知道
I don't know.
带我回家见家人
Taking me home to meet the family.
克服你自己
Get over yourself.
只是周日的晚餐
It's just Sunday dinner.
过去一个小时你一直在做什么
What have you been doing for the past hour?
试图找到他妈的
Trying to find the fucking...
它在哪里
Where is it?
这怎么可能呢
How is that possible?
我发现它的时候就是这样
That's how it was when I found it.
哦 你真他妈没用
Oh, you're fucking worthless.
把7 -16递给我
Just hand me a seven-16th.
嘿 我不是你的婊子
Hey, I'm not your bitch.
你是个漂亮的小贱人
And you're a pretty little bitch.
又叫我贱人了
Call me a bitch again, huh?
贱人 婊子
Bitch, bitch.
嗨 笨蛋
Hey, dipshits.
我们有同伴了
We got company.
哦 哦 哦 哦 天哪
Oh, oh, oh, oh, my.
小弟弟要带个女孩回家
Baby bro is bringing home a girl.
伙计们 这是艾比
Guys, this is Abby.
艾比 这是那对白痴双胞胎 泰勒和泰勒
Abby, these are the moron twins, Tyler and Taylor.
嗨
Hi.
兄弟 很明显
Fraternal, obviously.
我们也不是白痴
And we're not morons.
特拉维斯才是白痴
Travis is the moron.
你们能不能别这么混蛋
Can you guys not act like assholes just yet?
哦
Oh.
哥哥在他的女人面前乱说话
Brother's mouthing off in front of his woman.
你是个大块头 不是吗
You're a big guy, aren't you?
是啊 你是学校里的大人物 对吧
Yeah, you're the big man on campus, right?
这说不通啊
Doesn't make any sense.
这是有道理的
Well, this makes sense.
哦
Oh.
泰勒
Taylor!
眼镜蛇凯
Cobra kai!
退后 泰勒
Get back, Taylor.
所以不成熟
So immature.
你是阿比盖尔 对吧
Oh, you're Abigail, right?
嗯嗯
Mm-hm.
我是特伦顿
I'm, uh, Trenton.
最有魅力的马多克斯兄弟
The most attractive Maddox brother.
嘿
Hey.
有没有人告诉过你 你拥有最
Has anyone ever told you you have the most...
不
No!
No.
女士们 别在我自行车前
Ladies, not in front of my bike.
把它带到拳击场上
Take it in the ring.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
把我的工具放回原来的地方
Put my tools back where you found them.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
嘿 我是杰夫
Hey, I'm Jeff.
我是艾比
I'm Abby.
见到你很高兴
Nice to meet you.
你也一样
You too.
进来吧 谢谢
Come on inside. - Thanks.
那么 艾比
So, uh, Abby,
你尝过它的美味吗
have you ever experienced the deliciousness
肯塔基州的炸鸡
of fried chicken from Kentucky?
白痴 不是所有的鸡都是肯塔基产的
Moron, not every chicken is from Kentucky.
是的 是的
Yeah, it is.
这就是为什么他们叫它肯德基
That's why they call it Kentucky Fried Chicken.
这是怎么回事
What's going on here?
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
你回来
You're back.
怎么了 孩子们 哟
What's up, boys? - Yo.
嘿
Hey.
伙计 你来了
Dude, hey, you made it.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
抱歉 工作耽误了
Hey, sorry, uh, work ran late.
好吧 你一定是艾比吧
All right, you must be, um, is it Abby?
是的 你是托马斯 对吗
Yeah, and you're Thomas, right?
你是老大
You're the oldest.
崔维斯警告过你要小心我们吧
I see Travis warned you about us, huh?
有趣的对话 让我们开始吧
Riveting conversation, let's dig in.
是的 -是啊
Yeah. - Oh, yeah.
恩典
Grace.
特拉维斯
Travis.
哦 天父
Oh, Heavenly Father.
谢谢你的食物 因为我们记得饥饿的人
Thank you for the food, for we remember the hungry.
请照顾好我们亲爱的妈妈 黛安娜
Please look after our dear mother, Diane.
愿她安息
May she rest in peace.
阿们
Amen.
给我
Give me.
我们可以吗 好的
Can we? - Okay.
这些都是鸡腿吗 爸爸
Is this all drumsticks, Dad?
我想要乳房
I want breasts,
我想要乳房 -我要乳房
I want breasts. - I want breasts.
伙计们 伙计们 有个女士来了
Guys, guys, there's a lady present.
天啊 我很抱歉
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
哦 哇
Oh, wow.
他们今天很友好
They're being nice today.
这些都是很好的作品
Those are some good pieces.
真贴心 谢谢你们
Really sweet, thank you, guys.
我不想扫崔维斯的兴
Uh, I don't wanna rain on Travis's parade,
但我10点开始值班 所以我们开始谈正事吧
but my shift starts at 10, so let's get down to business.
10神 -那就像
10, God. - That's like...
我只是说如果你想玩 那就玩
I'm just saying if you wanna play, let's play.
我得赶紧揍你一顿
I'm gonna have to whoop your butt fast.
哦 是的
Oh, yeah.
我能拿点东西
I-I can carry some stuff.
好吧这个游戏叫德州扑克艾比
All right, the name of the game is Texas hold 'em, Abby,
你在吗
you in?
哦 那不是给我的
Oh, that's not for me.
饮料吗
Drinks?
是的
Yeah.
我要啤酒 那里有薯片
Beer for me and there's chips up there
还有蘸酱 你知道
and there's dip and there's like, you know,
只要你能带的
just whatever you can carry.
好吧
Okay.
成交 成交 成交 成交 成交 成交
Deal, deal, deal, deal, deal, deal.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我来拿芯片
Let me get the chip.
什么也没得到
Got nothing.
吃屎
Eat shit.
直上河 他又来了 伙计们
Straight on the river and he does it again, boys.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
艾比 你已经看了很久了
Abby, you've been watching a while.
你想加入吗
You wanna join?
哦 我没事
Oh, I'm okay.
别担心
Don't worry.
我们对这里的女士们放轻松点
We take it easy on the ladies over here.
如果你喜欢 我们可以玩钓鱼游戏
We can play Go Fish if you like.
其实我不觉得
You know, I actually don't think
问题是你们要对我宽容一点
it's a question of you guys going easy on me.
其实我觉得这是我的问题
I actually think it's a question of me
对你们好点
going easy on you guys.
哦
Oh.
好吧 你是认真的
Okay, you're being serious.
嗯嗯
Mm-hm.
好吧
Okay.
艾比 你最好别这么做
Abby, you might not wanna do that.
泰勒可能看起来像个白痴
Taylor may look like an idiot,
但他碰巧是镇上最好的扑克玩家之一
but he happens to be one of the best poker players in town.
哦 在城里
Oh, in town.
在县里
In the county.
哦 哇 县里
Oh, wow, the county.
他甚至在电视上表演过
He's even played on TV.
哦 在电视上
Oh, on TV.
真了不起 我不知道
That's pretty impressive, I don't know.
我们走吧
Let's go.
好吧
Okay.
折叠 初学者的运气
Fold, beginner's luck.
这不是初学者的运气
This is no beginner's luck.
我可没说过我是初学者
Well, I never said I was a beginner.
调用
Call.
冲洗
Flush.
一对a
Pair of aces.
是的
Yes!
哒 哒 哒 哒 哒 哒 哒
Da, da, da, da, da, da, da.
a和8 孩子们
Aces and eights, boys.
别告诉我
Don't tell me!
座无虚席啊
That's a full house.
是的 它是
Yes, it is.
你只是被骗了 兄弟
You just got hustled, bro.
不 只有我留着你的钱才算卖命
Well, no, it's only hustling if I keep your money.
哦
Oh.
哦 不 不 不
Oh, no, no, no.
亲爱的 那笔钱是你的
Sweetheart, that money's yours.
你光明正大地赢了
You won it fair and square.
大便
Shit.
你在哪里学的
Where did you learn to play?
首页
Home.
回家吗
Home?
在哪里
Where was that?
拉斯维加斯
Vegas.
我爸爸教我的
My dad taught me.
曾经是一个叫艾伯纳西的高赌注扑克玩家
Used to be a high-stakes poker player named Abernathy.
我记得在维加斯听过他的故事
I remember hearing stories about him in Vegas.
发生了什么事
What happened?
他有个女儿
Uh, he had this daughter.
到哪儿都跟着他
Went with him everywhere.
我觉得他妈妈抛弃了他
I think the mom walked out on him
所以他是独自抚养她长大的
so he was raising her on his own.
你的眼睛 即使你在走路
...your eyes even when you're shuffling.
当时她还太小 不能合法地玩
While she was way too young to play legally
但是 她可是个扑克天才
but man, she was a poker prodigy.
她愈演愈烈 他却愈演愈烈
As she got better, he got worse.
所以她只能保释他 即使他还是个孩子
So she was left bailing him out, even as a kid.
看着你对手的眼睛
Look your opponent in the eyes.
我记得这个
I remember this.
他们叫她幸运符
They called her Lucky Charms.
幸运的13
Lucky 13.
艾比 你一定听说过她吧
Abby, you must have heard of her, right?
她一定和你差不多大
She must be about your age.
毕竟 文章里出现的是你 不是吗
After all, this is you in the article, isn't it?
你是幸运13
You're Lucky 13?
我们被幸运13骗了吗
We just got hustled by Lucky 13?
不可能
No fucking way.
各位 我很抱歉
Guys, I'm sorry.
我发誓 我不是想骗你们什么的 我
I wasn't trying to hustle you guys or anything, I swear. I'm...
幸运13人在这房子里
Lucky 13's in this house?
是的
Yeah.
家里有13个幸运儿
Lucky 13 in the house!
Lucky 13 in the house.
艾比 能和你合个影吗
Abby, can I get a photo with you?
不 伙计们 那不是真的
No, guys, it wasn't really...
伙计们 伙计们 嘿
Guys, guys, hey.
你们表现得像一群女粉
You're acting like a bunch of fangirls.
别挡我的路
Get out of my way.
你是个迷妹
You're a fangirl.
她打败了我
She beat me.
你是个迷妹 快走
You're a fangirl, move!
闭嘴
Shut up!
把你的丑脸挪开
Get your ugly ass face out of the way!
我每晚都要在你身边
♪ I've gotta be near you every night ♪
每天的
♪ Everyday ♪
你表现得一副无辜的样子
You act like you're so fucking innocent.
我不会快乐 宝贝 -去你妈的
♪ I couldn't be happy baby ♪ - Fuck you!
还有别的办法吗
♪ Any other way ♪
他怎么能这样对泰莎
How could he do that to Tessa?
注射
Jab.
十字架
Cross.
你为什么这么高兴
Why are you so happy?
我不知道 我是个快乐的斗士 好吗
I don't know, I'm a happy fighter, okay?
不 不
No, no.
如果你在拳击场上真的很开心
If you were actually happy in the ring,
只要扇一巴掌就好了
it would be so easy to just slap
别傻笑了 -它会解除人们的武装
that smirk off. - It would disarm people.
刺拳 交叉
Jab, cross.
这次是有实际意义的
This time with actual meaning to it.
好吧 好吧 我懂了 我会生气的
Okay, okay, I get it, I'll be angry.
你能去吗
Well, can you go?
快走 快走 -我很生气
Go now, go now! - I'm angry, okay.
刺拳 十字拳 刺拳 十字拳
Jab, cross, jab, cross.
哦
Oh.
那一定是爱
♪ It must be love ♪
爱 爱
♪ Love, love ♪
没什么了
♪ Nothing more ♪
什么都没有
♪ Nothing less ♪
爱是最好的
♪ Love is the best ♪
就像我从来没和他这样的人约会过一样
Just like I've, I've never dated anyone like him
但当我和他在一起时 我只是
but when I'm with him, I just,
有时候我觉得他会是我永远的爱人
sometimes feel like he could be my forever person.
我不知道 他就是喜欢 让我笑
I don't know, he just like, makes me laugh
以这种方式 我不知道
in this way that like, I don't know,
比如特拉维斯能让你笑
like Travis makes you laugh.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
那是胡扯
That is bullshit.
我不知道
I don't know.
婊子 你知道的
Bitch, you know.
好吧 听着 我承认
Okay, yeah, look, I will admit
他的体格很吸引人
his physique is appealing.
His physique is appealing?
是的 他的体格很吸引人
Yes, his physique is appealing.
但我学会了不追求刺激
But I've learned not to court excitement
为了刺激
for the sake of excitement.
我是说 说实话 他看起来有点疯狂
I mean, truthfully, he seems a little crazy.
我们都知道我最不想看到的就是更疯狂的事
And we both know that the last thing I need is more crazy.
绝对的
Absolutely.
我
I...
啊
Ugh.
我想那是我的床
I believe that's my side of the bed.
我移动
I'm moving.
你完成作业了吗
Did you finish the homework?
是的 差不多了
Yeah, just about.
需要帮忙吗
You need any help?
不 我很好
Nah, I'm good.
别告诉我你要在床上剪脚趾甲
Please tell me you're not gonna clip your toenails in bed.
你会想念我的
♪ You're gonna miss me ♪
我听说两天后是某人的生日
So, I hear it's someone's birthday in two days.
你听到了 还是偷听到的
You hear, or you eavesdropped?
那是我和梅之间的事
That was between Mer and I.
噢
Ow!
那是私人谈话
That was a private conversation.
这伤害
That hurt.
你偷听真是活该
Well, it serves you right for eavesdrop.
Whoa -ho
Whoa-ho.
我刚从你嘴里问出什么了
What did I just get out of you there?
你是什么 半个牛头犬
What are you, half bulldog?
是你摸我的
Well, you groped me.
我没有摸你 那是偷猎
I did not grope you, that was a poach.
哦 你是个鼻涕虫
Oh, you are a snort.
我没有意识到这一点 -我不怕痒
I didn't realize this. - Mm, I'm not ticklish.
好了 不喜欢
Okay, don't.
你真的想玩这个吗
Do you really wanna play this?
好吧
Okay.
来吧
Come on.
好了 -这只是
There we go. - This is just.
你觉得这事会怎么结束
How do you think this was gonna end?
放开我
Get off me.
我会和你战斗 你知道的
I'll fight you, you know,
我要和你决斗 战斗
I'll fight you. - Fight?
哦 你
Oh, you.
噢
Ow!
你咬了我的奶头
You bit my tit.
哦 放松
Oh, relax.
这是一个小口
It was a nibble.
是啊 很疼
Yeah, well it hurt.
哦 是吗
Oh, did it?
你喜欢它
You loved it.
我确实挺喜欢的
I did kind of love it, yeah.
等等
Wait!
你好吗
You good?
我做得好吗
Am I good?
嗯嗯
Mm-hm.
不
No.
我只是有点困惑
Um, I'm just confused.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
这是个笑话
This is a joke.
别这样 特拉维斯
Oh, come on, Travis.
你不想谈谈吗
Don't you wanna talk about this?
说说看 为什么
Talk about it, why?
你想知道我对你的真实感受吗 艾比
You want to hear how I really feel about you, Abby?
不 我不知道
No, I-I don't.
艾比
Abby, then.
因为我和你感觉不一样
Because I don't feel the same way.
你就是在说谎
You're lying.
我不是
I'm not.
特拉维斯 你很粗俗 你很野蛮 你
Travis, you're vulgar, you're a brute, you're.
你能不能说我的名字 说我的名字 说我的名字
♪ Can you say my name, say my name, say my name ♪
触摸我
Touch me.
我要尿尿
I have to pee.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
等等 你要去哪
Wait, where you going?
我在边缘
I'm on the verge.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
宝贝 我在
Babe, I'm on...
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
嘘
Shh.
你没事吧
You okay?
不 不 我不好
No, no, I'm not okay.
特拉维斯和我 我们亲热得很激烈
Um, Travis and I, we made out kind of aggressively.
澄清
Clarify.
然后我抓住 他抓住了我的
And then I grabbed, he grabbed my.
我把他的手放在我的
I put his hand on my.
乳房吗
Breast?
不 更低
No, lower.
哦
Oh.
美国 我不知道该怎么办
America, I don't know what to do.
就好像 我脑子里的逻辑都没了
It's like, the logic goes out of my head.
如果我回去
If I go back in there,
我控制不了自己
I'm not gonna be able to stop myself.
这么说你确实喜欢他
So you do like him.
美国 我想我爱上他了
America, I think I'm in love with him.
嗨 艾比
Hey, Abby.
这是一个完全正常的姿势
This is a totally normal position
而我却一点都不放松
and I'm not flexing at all.
嘿 宝贝女儿
Hey, baby girl.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
她没事 她没事 她没事
She's okay, she's okay, she's okay.
她只是有点紧张
She's just nervous,
但我可以帮你克服紧张
but I can help you through your nervousness.
别这么说她
Don't read her like this.
太老套了
It's too corny.
你没有毒 你是个很酷的人
You're not toxic, you're a cool guy.
你真的很酷很强壮
You're really cool and strong.
你好 艾比
Hi, Abby.
给我一个拥抱
Give me a hug.
哦 不 那太可怕了
Oh, no, that's so scary.
特拉维斯
Travis?
不 我是说 他可能有
Yeah, no, I mean, he might have a.
人
Guys.
哦 等等
Oh, hold up.
你到底去哪了
Where the hell have you been?
出去了
Out.
天啊 你浑身酒气
Jesus, you reek of alcohol.
我养了一只猫
I got a cat.
我给它起名叫虎斑猫 它是只流浪狗
I named him Tabby, he's a stray.
我会为他杀人 他也会为我杀人
And I would kill for him, and he would kill for me,
不像我在这里认识的一些人
unlike some people I know in this house.
那是邻居的猫 朗普提泽
That's the neighbor's cat, Rumpleteazer.
不 不是 这是塔比
No it isn't this is Tabby?
我是说 兄弟 这里有个项圈
I mean, brah, it's got a collar right there.
大便
Shit.
好
Well.
嘿 芽
Hey, bud.
你还在这里干什么
The hell are you still doing here?
我整晚都在担心你
I was up all night worried about you.
这是丰富的
That's rich.
你不应该担心你男朋友什么的吗
Shouldn't you be worried about your boyfriend or something?
我的男朋友吗
My boyfriend?
是的 米克
Yeah, Mick.
没错 我看到你电脑上的短信了
That's right, I saw the text on your computer.
非常好 非常好
Very nice, very nice.
他给你发短信 你却待在这里
Staying here while he's texting you
"我爱你 我想你"
"I love you, I miss you."
真是个笑话
What a joke.
特拉维斯 米克是我爸爸
Travis, Mick is my dad.
你多久看一次我的短信
And how often are you going through my text messages?
"我能来看你吗"
"Can I come see you?" would make sense.
所以是你爸爸干的
So it was your dad?
不可能
No way.
我太糟糕了
That's terrible of me.
好吧 我误解了
Well, I misinterpreted that.
这是个好消息
That's great news.
这是好消息吗
Is it great news?
崔维斯 你侵犯了我的隐私
Travis, you invaded my privacy
然后你就转身离开了我
and then you turned around and ghosted me.
再见
Goodbye.
艾比 等等 等等
Abby, wait, wait.
对不起 对不起 对不起
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
我很嫉妒 我搞砸了
I-I was jealous, I messed up.
不 特拉维斯 你没有搞砸
No, Travis, you didn't mess up.
你只是向我展示了真实的你
If anything, you just showed me who you really are.
艾比 等等 我们能谈谈吗
Abby, wait, can we talk?
再见
Bye.
嘿
Hey.
有人告诉过你吗
Did anyone ever tell you
你是一个非常可爱的睡眠者
that you're a very cute sleeper?
嗨 帕克
Hi, Parker.
嗨
Hi.
特拉维斯在附近吗
Is Travis nearby?
我需要担心吗
Do I need to be worried?
嗯 不
Ugh, no.
好久不见了
It's been a while.
你过得怎么样
How-how have you been?
很糟糕的
Pretty shitty.
Postmates吗
Postmates?
我很乐意
I would love that.
所以 我花了五年级的大部分时间
So, I spent most of fifth grade
他的腿断了 他们不得不复位两次
with a broken leg that they had to reset twice.
所以我和医生们很熟
So I got to know the doctors pretty well,
意识到这就是我想做的
and realized that's what I wanted to do
用我的余生
with the rest of my life.
你想成为什么样的医生
What kind of doctor do you wanna be?
儿科医学
Pediatric medicine.
是啊 当然 因为是你
Right, yeah, of course, because it's you.
不管怎样 关于我就说这么多
Anyway, that's enough about me.
你长大后想做什么
What do you wanna be when you grow up?
我还在想办法
I'm still trying to figure it out.
非常好吃的拉面
Really good ramen.
你想离开这里吗
Do you wanna get out of here?
是的 是的 是的
Yes, yes, yes.
我答应了很多次 但还是答应了
I'm saying yes a lot, but yes.
就在这里
It is right up here.
我们不会又要表演了吧
We're not gonna a show again, are we?
我不会再犯那样的错误了
I would not make that mistake again.
就在这里
Right through here.
为什么这里这么黑
Why is it so dark in here?
惊喜
Surprise!
喔
Whoo.
好了 各位
All right, everybody.
去拿点饮料
Get some drinks.
打几针
Get some shots.
生日快乐 艾比
Happy birthday, Abby.
谢谢你
Thank you.
嘿 你感到惊讶吗
Hey, are you surprised?
是的
Yeah.
触地得分
Touchdown.
干得好 医生
And, uh, nice work, doc.
你也参与了吗
Were you in on this?
就在最后十分钟
Uh, only for the last 10 minutes.
谢普利发了全境通告找你
Shepley put out an APB for you.
宝贝 成功 成功
Babe, success, success.
打几针
Take some shots.
告诉过你会成功的
Told you this would work out,
不是吗 我说了 -你说了 真的
did I not, I said it. - You did, you really did.
是的
Yeah.
我去拿杯喝的 这个我来拿
I'm gonna grab us a drink and I will take this.
哦 谢谢
Oh, thank you.
你好吗 寿星 -嗨
How are you, birthday pal? - Hi.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这不是很棒吗
Isn't this great?
是的 是的
Yeah, yeah.
这些人是谁
Who are all these people?
嗯 不知道
Mm, no idea.
特拉维斯记在脑子里了
Travis got it in his head
这是他道歉的唯一方式
that this was the only way to say he was sorry
然后Shepley非常兴奋
and then Shepley got like really excited and,
我无法说服他们离开悬崖
and I couldn't talk them off the ledge.
他来了
There he is.
我应该去找崔维斯谈谈
I should probably go talk to Travis.
是的
Yeah.
再见 小鸟
Bye, little bird.
你忙吗
You busy?
嘿 这是快过生日的女孩
Hey, it's the almost birthday girl.
惊讶吗
Surprised?
是的 惊讶是保守的说法
Yeah, surprised is an understatement.
你甚至招募了帕克
You even recruited Parker.
他找到你了
Well, he found you.
我早该知道你们会在一起的
I should have known that you guys would be hanging out.
我可以信任他
Well, I can trust him.
酷
Cool.
嗯 好吧 我要
Um, well, I'm gonna...
是的 玩得开心
Yeah, have fun.
是的
Yeah.
你没事吧
You okay?
不
No.
我需要爽一爽
I need to get fucked up.
我可以做到
I can make that happen.
投篮 投篮 投篮 投篮 投篮
Shot, shot, shot, shot, shot.
哇
Whoo!
噢
Ooh!
哦 两个 哦
Oh, two. - Oh.
哦 好吧 -该死 姑娘
Shoot, oh, all right. - Damn, girl.
哇
Whoo!
就是这样的夜晚
It's that kind of night.
哦
Oh.
慢下来
Slow down.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
队伍排得很长
The line was interminable.
哦
Oh.
我有 我有梅洛酒
I got, I got us merlots.
帕克 集中注意力
Parker, concentrating.
呃
Uh.
你为什么这么擅长这个
Why are you so good at this?
我会在那边的沙发上
I'll be over there on the sofa.
你以前玩过这个
You played this before.
你玩了这个
You played this.
如果你看看奥巴马医改下的医疗保健系统
If you look at the health care system under Obamacare,
很明显 我们在碰撞的轨道上
we are obviously on a collision course.
我知道 这很糟糕
I know, it's bad.
哦 别这样 -不不不不不不不不
Oh, come on. - No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
艾比 艾比 艾比
Abby, Abby, Abby.
你很好
You're good...
他有
He's got.
不 我不想要孩子
No, I don't want kids!
你说 你不想要孩子是什么意思
What do you, what do you mean you don't want kids?
这是 -我不想要孩子
It's... - I don't want kids.
我不想 为什么
I don't wanna. - Why?
我从来不知道这些
I never knew this.
我不想要孩子
I don't want any kids.
我想要五个孩子
I want like five kids.
五个孩子吗 是的
Five kids? - Yes.
我要小泰德
I want Ted Junior.
别问 泰德一号是谁
Don't, who is Ted One?
米利森特
Millicent.
我不是婴儿工厂 -这是
I'm not a baby factory. - This is,
这是整个的
this is like whole.
我不会给我的孩子取名叫米莉森特
And I'm not naming my kid Millicent.
这就是生活的意义
This is the point of life.
我讨厌米莉森特
I hate Millicent.
我恨你
Well, I hate you.
我更恨你
I hate you more.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
不
No.
不 都结束了
No, it's over.
我再也不会把心给任何人了
I'm never giving my heart to anyone ever again.
不
No!
不 别这么说
No, don't say that.
你只需要跳舞
You just need to dance.
你只需要用舞蹈把烦恼赶走
You just need to dance your troubles away.
照我做的做
Just do what I do.
噢 嗨
Oh, hi.
宝贝 我很抱歉
Babe, I am so sorry.
我不知道我为什么要那么说
I don't know why I said that out there.
我很抱歉 我很抱歉
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
你想去补上床吗
Do you wanna go and have make-up sex?
是的 现在吗
Yes, right now?
是的 我们走吧 好的
Yeah, let's go. - Okay.
玩得开心
Have fun.
这太棒了 我要走了
This has been great, I'm gonna get out of here.
不 来吧 和我跳舞
No, come on, dance with me.
我 我没心情
I'm-I'm not in the mood.
哦 别这样 放松点
Oh, come on, loosen up.
哦 我知道
Oh, I know.
我twerking
I'm twerking.
呃
Uh.
男孩们喜欢跳电臀舞
The boys like the twerking.
不 不 你不是
No, no, you're not.
不 这是 嗯 是的 -这是电臀舞
No, this is, uh, yeah. - This is twerking.
Twerking
Twerking.
是的 是的 很好
Yeah, yeah, it's good.
来吧 玩得开心 你一点都不有趣
Come on, have fun, you're not fun.
来吧 放松点 玩得开心
Come on, loosen up, have fun.
来吧
Come on.
他在里屋
He's in the back room.
原谅我吗
Excuse me?
特拉维斯
Travis?
你要找的人
The guy you're looking for.
不 我和你一起来的
No, I came here with you.
哇
Wow!
哦 你居然退缩了
Oh, you actually recoiled.
你让我措手不及
You just caught me off guard.
对自己诚实
Be honest with yourself
和崔维斯一起把这事做完
and see this thing through with Travis.
他不适合我
He's not good for me.
你一直这么对自己说
You keep telling yourself that.
你好 你好
Hello, hello.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thank you.
嘿 你他妈在干什么
Hey, what the fuck are you doing?
你听说过酒精中毒吗
You heard of alcohol poisoning?
你一小时前就达到两位数了
You hit double digits an hour ago.
你在数什么
What are you, counting?
是的 真的
Yeah, actually.
你今晚喝得够多了
You've had enough for tonight.
不
No.
你今天吃东西了吗
Have you had anything to eat today?
是的 汤
Yes, soup.
汤吗 汤
Soup? - Soup.
好吧 你不会有好下场的
Okay, well, that's gonna end badly for you.
戒酒
Stop drinking.
不
No.
你太固执了
You're beyond stubborn.
哦 我很抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry
我不是你那种卑躬屈膝的小女孩
I'm not one of your subservient little wenches.
你知道这一切拼凑起来有多难吗
Do you know how hard this was to put together?
我做这一切都是为了你
I did all this for you.
我可没让你这么做
I didn't ask you to do any of this.
我知道 这就是重点
I-I know, that's the point.
我这么做是因为我在乎你
I did it because I care about you.
崔维斯 你来晚了
Well, Travis, you're too late.
明天赌局就结束了 你再也不用见到我了
Tomorrow the bet's over, and you never have to see me again.
大便
Shit.
艾比 等等
Abby, wait.
走开
Go away!
站着不动
Stand still.
我 你一团糟
I, you're a mess.
你为什么要跑
Why are you running?
你真是一团糟
You're a mess.
我比你快 -不不不
I'm faster than you. - No, no, no.
艾比
Abby!
走开 不
Get off, no!
好 好 好
Okay, okay, okay.
你知道吗 你真是个懦夫
You know, you are such a coward.
你真是个懦夫 -你在说胡话
You're such a coward. - You're not making any sense.
不 你不是
No, you're not.
你刚从我身边跑开
You just run away from me.
而不是问我米克是谁
Rather than ask me who Mick was.
你就这么 你就这么跑了然后就把我扔了
You just-you just run away and then you just throw me
为我的生日准备的惊喜生日派对
this really big surprise birthday party for my birthday.
你觉得一切都会好起来的
And you think it's all gonna be okay
我一个人都不认识
where I don't even know anybody.
然后你整晚都不理我
And then you just ignore me all night.
你以为我会原谅你吗
And you think I'm just gonna forgive you?
因为你给我办了个惊喜生日派对
Because you throw me this really big surprise birthday party
在我一个人都不认识的地方过生日
for my birthday where I don't know anybody.
你已经说过了
You said that already.
别再告诉我该怎么做了
Stop telling me what to do!
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
首先 我确实向你道歉了
First off, I did apologize to you
我也想跟你谈谈
and I tried to have a conversation with you too.
但你却跑去图书馆了
But you ran off to the fucking library
后来又带着帕克出现了
only to show up later with Parker
然后继续把事情搞得一团糟
and then proceed to get beyond fucked up.
所以 小猪猪 你得离我远点
So, pidge, you're gonna have to walk away from me
因为我不能离开你
because I can't walk away from you.
美丽
Beautiful.
我什么时候吃过面条
When did I have noodles?
我想我受够了
I think I'm done.
好吧
Okay.
哦 对不起
Oh, sorry.
哦 你没事的
Oh, you're all right.
好吧 我真的希望你做完了
Well, I sure hope you're done.
我不确定你里面还有什么要吐的
I'm not sure if you have anything left in there to throw up.
嘿 你想亲热吗
Hey, you wanna make out?
不完全是
Not really, no.
我不喜欢
I don't.
你知道这最好的是什么吗 鸽子
You know what the best part about this is, pigeon?
嗯
Hm.
你不会记得这一切的
You're not gonna remember any of this.
我不是吗
I'm not?
不
No.
所以当我告诉你我疯狂地爱着你
So when I tell you that I'm madly in love with you.
我不会记得的
I won't remember.
但我是认真的
But I really mean it.
嗯
Hm.
你想去国际煎饼屋吗
Do you wanna go to International House of Pancakes
还有煎饼
and get pancakes?
是吗
Yeah?
你想去吗
You wanna go?
我喜欢煎饼 -天啊 真是个好主意
I love pancakes. - Oh, man, what a great idea.
我来扶你起来 -你想去吗
I'm gonna get you up. - Do you wanna go?
我要放你鸽子 -我想去吃煎饼
I'm gonna stand you up. - Oh, I wanna go to pancakes.
好吧 我要煎饼
Okay, I want pancakes.
我给你买了件干净的衬衫
I got you a clean shirt instead,
我马上回来 -谢谢 太好了
I'll be back. - Thank you, that's very nice.
嗯
Um.
我是个怪物
I'm a monster.
好吧 我来帮你
Okay, let me help you.
我卡住了 帮帮我
I'm stuck, help me..
是的 -谢谢
Yeah. - Thank you.
好了 穿上这个
Okay, there we go, put this on.
转身
Turn around.
我看上去还是很体面的
I'm decent.
只是开玩笑
Just kidding.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我抓住你了 -把衣服穿上
I got you. - Put your shirt on.
我抓住你了 -穿上
I got you. - Put it on.
我正在穿呢
I'm putting it on.
好吧
Okay.
好的 开始了
Okay, it's on.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
哦 我不能相信
Oh, I can't trust.
我又抓到你了
I got you again.
你做到了 你抓住了我
You did, you got me,
我真的很想再看看
and I really wanna look again,
但你应该把衣服穿上
but you should put your shirt on.
今晚我是个小恶作剧者
I'm a little prankster tonight.
我得说 你很傻
You are very silly, I'll say that.
好吧 你做到了 我真为你骄傲
Okay, you did it, I'm so proud of you.
我去给你倒点水 好吗
I'm gonna get you some water, okay?
我马上回来 -你人真好
I'll be back. - You're so nice.
谢谢你
Thank you,
你真的很好 -我很贴心
you're really nice. - I'm very sweet.
谢谢 -你爸爸是谁
Thanks. - Who's your daddy?
嘿 宝贝
Hey, baby.
你好 米克
Hi, Mick.
你好吗
How are you?
今天是我的生日
It's my birthday.
我只是在想你会不会打电话来
I was just wondering if you were gonna call.
我知道今天是你的生日
I know it's your birthday.
我 我想来看你
I, uh, I wanted to come see you
但我不知道你在哪里
but I have no idea where you are.
我在萨克拉门托上大学
I'm in college in Sacramento.
大学怎么样
How's college?
你好吗
How are you doing?
我很好
I'm good.
我没跟你说过话
I haven't talked to you
我真的很想念和你说话
and I-I-I really miss talking to you.
Pidge吗
Pidge?
哦 我得走了
Oh, I have to go.
我爱你 爸爸 再见
I love you, Dad, bye.
现在几点了
What time is it?
一个
One.
下午
In the afternoon?
我怎么没宿醉呢
How am I not hung over?
我强行灌了一升水
Well, I forced a liter of water
和两片布洛芬一起咽下喉咙
down your throat along with two ibuprofens
在你睡觉之前
before you went to sleep.
怎么啦
What?
只是有一天晚上 你喝醉了
It's just that one night, you're drunk.
然后第二天晚上 我喝醉了
Then the next night, I'm drunk.
是啊 我们不是很合拍 对吧
Yeah, we're not really in sync, are we?
我们就像个灾难
We're like a disaster.
你知道的
You know,
我在想我们可以开始这个生日
just thinking we can kick this birthday off
床上还有早餐
with some breakfast in bed.
我想喝杯咖啡
I would love a coffee.
马上就来 -谢谢
Coming right up. - Thank you.
哦
Oh.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我在想既然今天是我的生日
You know I was thinking since it's my birthday
也是我们作为室友在一起的最后一晚
and our last night together as roommates
也许我们可以做一些特别的事情
that maybe we do something special.
你有什么想法
What do you have in mind?
让我们看看魔法抽屉
Let's look in the magic drawer.
足底按摩
A foot massage.
你想要什么都行
Anything you want.
太多
Too much?
不 很好 很好
No, it's good, it's good.
真的很好吃
It's really good.
再来一次
Do it again.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
也许更轻
Maybe lighter.
Maybe lighter,
更轻、更轻 -好吧 好吧 好吧
lighter, lighter. - Okay, okay, okay.
是的
Yeah.
这很好
That's good.
我的小腿有点疼
My calf's kind of hurting.
你想让我这么做
And you want me to?
是的 请
Yes, please.
是啊 感觉很好
Yeah, that feels good.
还有别的地方需要我按摩吗
Is there anywhere else you'd want me to massage?
在这里
Here.
而且
And,
也许在这里
maybe here.
我可以告诉你为什么
♪ I can show you why ♪
摩托车血 大多觉得你很强悍
♪ Motorcycle blood, mostly think you're tough ♪
但我知道里面的路
♪ But I know the way inside ♪
你眼中的秘密
♪ Secret in your eyes ♪
让我占用你的时间
♪ Let me take your time ♪
到这里来
Come here.
把这个拿下来
Take this off.
到这里来
Come here.
对我有用 -嗯嗯
Works for me. - Mm-hm.
现在把这些拿掉
Now take these off.
好的 我试试
Yeah, I'll try.
好吧
Okay.
是的 看着我
Yeah, look at me.
一个
One.
两个
Two.
我不耐烦了
I got impatient.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
啊哈
Uh-huh.
它在吗
Is it in?
我抓住你了
I got you.
是啊 你说了
Yeah, you did.
闭嘴 亲亲我
Shut up and just kiss me.
你已经把我累坏了
Well, you've exhausted me officially.
我想我要去睡觉了
I think I'm gonna go to sleep.
晚安 艾比
Good night, Abby.
晚安 特拉维斯
Good night, Travis.
艾比
Abby?
艾比令人惋惜
Abby Abernathy.
早上好
Good morning.
我能帮你吗
Can I help you?
这可能听起来很奇怪
Uh, this might sound weird,
但我需要你跟我一起去
but I'm gonna need you to come with me.
是啊 不 那是不可能的
Yeah, no, that's not going to happen.
如果我客气地问呢
What if I asked nicely?
祝你过得愉快
Have a nice day.
是关于你爸爸的
It's about your dad.
我的爸爸
My dad?
是的
Yeah.
他怎么样了
What about him?
他下错了赌注 还欠我老板人情
He's placing bad bets and owes my boss.
如果你不跟我来 他们会打断他的腿
They're gonna break his legs if you don't come with me.
怎么啦 -嗨
What? - Hey.
你们来了 你们去哪了
There you guys are, where have you been?
怎么了 伙计
What's going on, man?
天啊
Geez.
艾比的消失了
Abby's disappeared.
现在帮我找找线索什么的
Now help me look for a clue or anything.
首先 别对我大喊大叫
First of all, don't yell at me.
其次 艾比还有很多事你不知道
Second of all, there's a lot about Abby that you don't know.
我什么都知道
I know everything.
我知道她是幸运13
I know that she's Lucky 13,
现在我知道她的床垫里装满了钱
and now I know that she packed her mattress full of money.
等等 我正在追踪她的位置
Hang on, I'm tracking her location.
她要去拉斯维加斯了
She's headed to Vegas.
拉斯维加斯吗
Vegas?
这可不妙
This isn't good.
等等 嘿 那是我的手机
Wait, hey, that's my phone!
给自己买一个新的
Buy yourself a new one.
迪克
Dick.
怎么啦
What?
感觉我只是
♪ Feeling like I'm only ♪
感觉自己像个小鸡
♪ Feeling like I'm chick ♪
像小鸡一样
♪ Like a chick ♪
活得像个疯子一样
♪ Livin' like I'm crazy ♪
有人听到吗
♪ Does anybody hear ♪
嘿
Hey.
嗨 米克
Hey, Mick.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你欠本尼多少钱
How much do you owe Benny?
十万美元
A hundred grand.
100000美元 爸爸 -我知道 我知道
$100,000, Dad? - I know, I know.
你在开玩笑吗 爸爸
Are you kidding me, Dad?
这些都是我做的 我发誓
I'm doing all this stuff, I swear.
我参加了匿名赌徒协会和匿名债务人协会
I'm-I'm doing Gamblers Anonymous and Debtors Anonymous.
我我已经完成 -只要你动 它就会起作用
I've-I've complete. - It works if you work it.
他们不是这么说的吗 米克
Isn't that what they say, Mick?
你好 艾比
Hello, Abby.
你玩得怎么样
How's your game?
我退休了
I'm retired.
阿比盖尔 匿名大学生
Oh, Abigail, anonymous college student.
看在你父亲的份上
Well, uh, for your father's sake,
我希望时间不会太长 因为他欠我十万
I hope it's a short time because he owes me 100 grand
今晚午夜之前
by midnight tonight.
来吧
Come on.
你爸连钱都不肯借给他
Your own dad wouldn't even lend him any money.
你知道他有问题
You know he has a problem.
不像我父亲 愿他安息
Unlike my father, may he rest in peace,
我不是在开日托所 我是在做生意
I'm not running a daycare, I'm running a business.
今晚之前要十万美金是不可能的
Well, 100 grand by tonight is impossible.
我们都知道 以你的才华
We both know, with your talent,
你一天就能做好
you can make that in a day.
我以前看你在地下30分钟赢了3万美元
I used to watch you win 30 grand in 30 minutes underground.
你以为你在跟谁说话
Who do you think you're talking to?
我是未成年
I'm underage.
如果我被抓到 我就得从大学退学
If I get caught, I have to drop out of college.
你在这里住得够久了 孩子
You've lived here long enough, kiddo.
你知道怎么避免被抓
You know how to avoid getting caught.
我们一定有别的办法处理这件事
There has to be another way that we can handle this.
就是这样 但你不会喜欢的
There it is, but you're not gonna like it.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey!
不 不 不 请不要 -我来 我来
No, no, no, no, please no! - I'll do it, I'll do it!
很高兴再次见到你 阿比盖尔
Good to see you again, Abigail.
米克
Mick.
嘿 自助餐吃够了
Hey, enough with the buffet.
给她开个房间
Get her a room.
离她远点
Leave her the fuck alone.
我们走吧
Let's go.
来吧 把上衣脱掉
Come on, take the top off.
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
哇 哇 哇
Wow, wow, wow.
你照我说的做了吗
Did you do what I asked?
是的 就像你指示的那样
Yeah, just like you instructed.
你确定要留在这里吗
Are you sure you wanna stay here?
贝拉吉奥有更大的鲸鱼
There are bigger whales at the Bellagio.
他们会认出我的
They'll recognize me there.
我想低调点
I'm trying to stay under the radar.
还有什么事吗 陛下
Anything else, Your Majesty?
是的 给服务员200英镑
Yeah, give the waitress 200
开始往我的饮料里加水
to start watering down my drinks
去外面等我叫你
and go wait outside until I call you.
你说对了
You got it.
嘿
Hey.
你们在玩扑克吗
Are you guys playing poker?
不 是轮盘赌
No, it's roulette.
至少得有五千块的进账
There's a minimum buy-in of five grand.
好吧 《狮子王》
Ooh, okay, Lion King.
看看你 你看起来不错
Look at you, you look nice.
但这是一个高风险的房间
But this is a high-stakes room.
帮你自己个忙 去一楼吧
Do yourself a favor and go to the main floor
然后挑一个闪亮的老虎机
and pick out a shiny slot machine.
我不能回主楼了
I can't go back to the main floor.
你看 我在参加一个单身派对
You see, I'm at this bachelorette party
谢丽尔邀请了这个混蛋特里
and Cheryl invited this twat, Terry,
因为莱尔在万圣节上了我而恨我的人
who hates me because Lyle finger-banged me on Halloween,
我要为自己辩护 我以为他们是分开的
which in my defense I thought that they were separated.
我的振动棒呢
Where's my vibrator?
嗯
Huh?
嘘 这是一手好牌吗
Psst, is this a good hand?
你为什么不说话
What's up with the silent treatment?
克里夫 我喜欢你的老虎衬衫
Hey, Cliff, I like your tiger shirt.
还是猎豹
Or is it cheetah?
你能安静点吗
Can you be quiet?
我能安静点吗
Can I be quiet?
你能安静点吗
Can you be quiet?
我像老鼠一样安静
I'm as quiet as a mouse.
混蛋 说什么
Asshole, say what?
怎么啦
What?
完全正确
Exactly.
我有两张黑牌
I've got two black cards.
这样好吗
Is that good?
你得亮出你的底牌
You gotta show your hand.
卡
The cards!
你在开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.
嘿 悬崖
Hey, Cliff.
阻止它
Stop it.
请
Please.
Rawr
Rawr.
好吧 我要去见我的朋友了
Okay, well, I'm gonna go meet up with my peeps.
这是真的 伙计们
It's been real, fellas.
就像我爸爸常说的
And like my dad used to say,
如果你不能在前30秒内认出那个笨蛋
if you can't spot the chump in the first 30 seconds,
那你就是笨蛋了
then you're the chump.
再见
Bye.
女士吗
Ma'am?
穿蓝裙子的那个
You in the blue dress?
停止
Stop.
我明白了
I gotcha.
杰西
Jesse.
我完全理解你 -嗨
I totally got you. - Hi.
到这里来
Come here.
你吓到我了
Oh, you scared me.
我敢打赌
I bet I did.
是的
Yeah.
天啊 你看起来棒极了
Jesus, you look fantastic.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你也是
So do you.
谢谢
Thanks.
对 保安 对吧
Yeah, security, right?
太好了
Great.
我就知道我该邀请你参加舞会
Man, I knew I should have asked you to prom.
对吧 -说真的
Right? - For real.
我 我有件事要去办
Um, well, I have a, I have a thing to get to.
哦 对了
Oh, yeah, right.
我能给你打电话吗
Can I call you?
是的 我很乐意
Yeah, I would love that.
我有相同的数字
I have the same number.
好的 我会给你打电话的
Yeah, I'll give you a call.
我们待会再出去玩
We'll hang out later.
太棒了
Awesome.
还有一件事
Just one more thing.
是吗
Yeah?
我需要你把这些芯片给我
I'm gonna need you to give me these chips.
原谅我吗
Excuse me?
来吧 艾比
Come on, Abby.
你未成年
You're underage.
你知道未成年是不能赌博的
You know you can't gamble when you're underage.
这是非法的
It's illegal.
我不想看到你惹上麻烦
I don't wanna see you get in trouble.
请杰西
Jesse, please.
我需要这笔钱
I-I need this money.
这是我的工作
This is my job.
我也不想看到你进监狱
And I would hate to see you go to jail.
艾比 把薯条给我
Abby, give me the chips.
我会在我老板面前掩护你的 好吗
I'll totally cover you with my boss, okay?
打电话给我
Call me.
嘿
Hey.
这是艾比
It's Abby.
你在俱乐部吗
Are you at the club?
怎么了 你还好吗
Why, are you okay?
我被抓住了
I got caught.
怎么啦
What?
听我说 爸爸
Listen to me, Dad.
离开俱乐部
Get out of the club.
滚出城去
Get out of town.
不要用手机
Don't use your cell phone.
不要使用你的信用卡
Don't use any of your credit cards
有了一次性手机给我发短信 好吗
and text me when you get a burner phone, okay?
我们会想办法的
We'll figure it out.
我想我今晚就走
I guess I'll leave tonight.
我将徒步去丹佛
I'll hike to Denver.
我很抱歉 爸爸
I'm so sorry, Dad.
我让你失望了
I let you down.
是你打电话给我的
You called me.
你说你拿了我的钱
You said you had my money.
我拿了你的钱
I had your money,
然后被杰西·维维罗斯抢走了
and then it was taken from me by Jesse Viveros.
那怎么会是我的问题呢
And that is my problem how?
米克在哪里
Where's Mick?
他走了 但我们会找到他的
He's gone, but we'll find him.
去找杰西吧
Just go find Jesse.
杰西拿了你的钱
Jesse has your money.
我不是慈善机构 我也不跑腿
I'm not a charity, and I don't run errands.
大便
Shit.
你知道吗
You know what?
艾比 我喜欢你
Abby, I like you.
你人很好
You're nice.
那你为什么不呢
So why don't you?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
哦 我是同性恋
Oh, I'm gay.
相信我 你不是我喜欢的类型
Trust me, you're not my type.
我会赞助你所有的入场费
I will sponsor all of your entrance fees.
加州的法定年龄是18岁
The legal age in California is 18,
利润我们五五分
and we'll split the profits 50-50.
我可不想靠打扑克为生
Well, I don't wanna play poker for a living.
我只想上大学
I just wanna go to college.
我给你一个妥协
I'm offering you a compromise.
艾比
Abby!
搞什么鬼 -特拉维斯
What the fuck? - Travis?
安全 -你没事吧
Security. - Are you okay?
你得马上离开 好吗
Hey, you got to leave right now, okay?
我是戴恩 我要碾碎你
I'm Dane and I'm going to crush you!
怎么啦
What?
特拉维斯
Travis?
这是你的
That's your one.
你很好
You're good.
出租车 -打给我 兄弟
Taxi. - Call me, bro.
鸽子
Pigeon?
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
搞什么鬼
What the heck?
别跟我说话
Don't talk to me.
为什么
Why?
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
你能和我谈谈吗
Will you talk to me?
艾比 停止
Abby, stop!
怎么啦
What?
你想要什么
What do you want?
我 嗯
I, uh...
你知道你刚刚做了什么吗
Do you have any idea what you just did?
我不会让他们伤害你的
I wasn't gonna let them hurt you.
他们没有伤害我 我很好
They weren't hurting me, I was fine.
我在自己处理这件事
I was handling it on my own.
我怎么知道
How am I supposed to know
当你把一切都保密的时候
when you keep everything a secret?
我帮你找到了拉斯维加斯的一家脱衣舞俱乐部
I had to track you down to a strip club in Vegas.
有一天你穿得像个修女
One day you're dressed like a nun,
然后你戴着这个
and then you're wearing this.
你到底是谁
Who the hell are you?
神
God.
我爱你
I love you.
你爱我吗
You love me?
你不了解我
You don't know me.
这不是真的
That's not true.
不管你在经历什么 我们都能解决
Whatever you're going through, we can figure it out.
我不想弄明白
I don't wanna figure it out.
我这辈子疯的够多了
I've had enough crazy in my life.
我不想再疯狂了
I don't want any more crazy.
崔维斯 你让我抓狂
And Travis, you make me crazy!
狗屎
Shit!
把它弄掉 弄掉
Get it off, get it off.
我尝试
I'm trying.
大便
Shit.
到这里来
Come here.
我好饥渴 我好饥渴
I'm so horny, I'm so horny.
我会努力的
I'll try!
好吧 我在努力 我在努力
Okay, I'm trying, I'm trying!
哦 狗屎
Oh, shit.
嘿 那边他妈的发生什么事了
Hey, what the fuck is going on over there?
把这些拿掉
Get these off.
你的纽扣怎么了
What's wrong with your button?
嘿 小声点 我们要睡觉了
Hey, keep it down, we're trying to sleep.
哦 哦 我的天啊
Oh, oh, my gosh.
真抱歉 你还好吗
I'm so sorry, you all right?
我只是需要
I-I-I just needed
脱掉我的鞋子 -没事 过来
to take off my shoe. - It's okay, come here.
哦
Aw.
嘿 别闹了
Hey, knock it off!
耶稣
Jesus.
那边发生什么事了
What's going on over there?
不
No.
回去 -是的
Go back. - Yeah.
哦 不 在这里
Oh, no, in here.
是的
Yeah.
把这个拿下来
Take this off.
帮我拿一下
Help me get it.
是的
Yeah.
不
No.
你介意吗 好的
Do you mind? - Okay.
对 放进去
Yeah, put it in.
我认为它不合适
I don't think it's in.
我不认为它在里面 我不认为
I-I don't think it's in, I don't think.
它不在
It's not in.
噢
Ow!
哦 对不起
Oh, sorry.
好吧 好吧
Ow, okay, okay.
不 等等 我们换一下 换一下
Yeah, no, hold on, let's switch, switch.
噢
Ow!
我什么都感觉不到
I can't feel anything.
不 不
No, no.
我们离开这里吧
Let's get out of here.
好吧
Okay.
艾比 米克还欠我十万呢
Abby, Mick still owes me 100 grand
这是你的责任
and it's on you.
打电话给我
Call me.
艾比
Abby.
不 是她男朋友
No, it's her boyfriend.
我知道她欠你钱
Look, I-I know that she owes you money,
但我想我有办法还给你
but I think I have a way to get it back to you.
我在听
I'm listening.
哦 哦 哦 哦 哦 哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
特拉维斯
Travis?
怎么啦
What?
鸽子 别生气
Pigeon, don't be mad.
我和本尼做了笔交易
I worked out a deal with Benny.
今晚我要为他而战 帮你还债
I'm gonna fight for him tonight and settle your debt.
你和你爸爸没事了
You and your dad are off the hook.
我把租来的车落在停车场了
I left a rental car in the parking garage
等着你回家
for you to get home.
我很快就回来了
I'll be back before you know it.
大便
Shit.
是崔维斯 你知道该怎么做
It's Travis, you know what to do.
是我 给我回电话
Hey, it's me, call me back.
你根本不知道自己惹上了什么麻烦
You have no idea what you've gotten yourself into.
看来你找到我的新车了
I see you found my new car.
很恶心 对吧
Pretty sick, right?
是的 很好
Yeah, it's nice.
里面空间很大 我喜欢
Tons of room in there, I like that.
是的 男人
Yeah, man.
所以一切顺利吗
So it went okay?
哦 她告诉你了
Oh, she told you about it.
把芯片给我 没问题
Handed over the chips, no problem.
那你觉得她现在会怎么做
So what do you think she's gonna do now?
她要开始为本尼工作还是怎样
She gonna start working for Benny or what?
啊 是的
Ah, yeah,
我觉得她现在没有太多选择
I don't think she has much of a choice at this point.
我听过的最伟大的事情之一是
One of the greatest things that I ever heard is
如果你在30秒内没发现那个笨蛋
if you don't spot the chump in the first 30 seconds,
那你就是笨蛋
then you are the chump.
我 我想来看你
I, uh, I wanna come see you
但我不知道你在哪里
but I have no idea where you are.
我在上大学
I'm in college.
是关于你爸爸的
It's about your dad.
米克今晚午夜前还欠我十万
Mick still owes me 100 grand by midnight tonight.
我需要你把这些芯片给我
I'm gonna need you to give me these chips.
滚出俱乐部 滚出小镇 好吗
Get out of the club, get out of town, okay?
我们会想办法的
We'll figure it out.
我想我今晚就走 徒步去丹佛
I guess I'll leave tonight, I'll hike to Denver.
艾比 她看起来很性感
You know, Abby, she's looking pretty hot.
你能不能别谈我女儿 谢谢
Can you not talk about my daughter, thanks.
不不 我知道
No, no, I know.
我只是说"该死"
I was just like, "Dang."
艾比 你在 -你这个混蛋
Ho, Abby, what are you.. - You son of a bitch.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
丹芙怎么样 米克
How's Denver, Mick?
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
噢
Ow.
大便
Shit.
显然 我不在丹佛
Obviously, I'm not in Denver.
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.
我要去登 噢
I'm going to Den, ow!
给你两秒钟坦白
You have two seconds to come clean.
坦白交代
To come clean about wha-ow!
你 本尼 杰西 你们陷害了我
You, Benny, Jesse, you guys set me up
从一开始 不是吗
from the beginning, didn't you?
艾比 艾比 我
Abby, Abby, I...
你又不欠本尼钱
You don't owe Benny any fucking money.
看看我 我是个老男人了
Look at me, I'm an old fucking man.
我弹得没你好 好吗
I can't play as good as you play, okay?
我需要钱 我需要钱来生活
And I need money, I need money to live.
那就像正常人一样找份工作
Then get a job like a normal person.
我知道这看起来不太好 好吗
I know this doesn't look good, okay?
我明白了
I get it.
这看起来不太好 -对 对 对
This does not look good. - Yeah, right, yeah.
我爱你
I love you.
出去
Get out.
滚出去 好的
Get out! - Okay.
滚出去
Get out!
从我的生活中消失
Out of my life.
滚出去
Get out!
我可以拿我的包吗
Can I get my bag?
滚出去
Get out!
艾比
Abby!
是崔维斯 你知道该怎么做
It's Travis, you know what to do.
崔维斯 回我电话
Travis, call me back.
你不需要战斗
You don't have to fight.
没人欠本尼什么
No one owes Benny anything.
现在是今晚的第一场活动
And now, for the first event this evening
我们有很特别的东西
we have something very special,
挑战者 特拉维斯"疯狗"马多克斯
the challenger, Travis "Mad Dog" Maddox!
伙计 当你说来维加斯的时候
Man, when you said come out to Vegas,
我以为你指的是百乐宫
I thought you meant the Bellagio.
我要上你妈 好吗
Hey, I'm gonna fuck your mother, all right?
疯狗
Mad Dog.
谢谢 是的
Thanks, yeah.
她已经死了 所以你不能
Well, she's dead, so you can't.
封锁马上就要开始了
The lockdown is about to begin
倒数五 四 三 二
in five, four, three, two.
有什么办法可以帮我吗
Is there any way I can?
妓女 妓女 好的
Whore, whore! - Okay.
好吧 我走了 我走了
Okay, I'm going, I'm going.
现在是冠军 切尔诺贝利
And now, the champion, Chernobyl!
搞什么鬼
What the fuck.
你会死的
You're going to die.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谁死了 谁就输了
Whoever dies, loses.
切尔诺贝利 切尔诺贝利
Chernobyl, Chernobyl.
最近怎么样
How's it going?
切尔诺贝利 切尔诺贝利
Chernobyl, Chernobyl.
太棒了
Awesome.
来吧 我们能走了吗
Come on, can we go?
请
Please.
闭嘴
Shut up!
这太糟糕了
This is gonna suck.
是的 哇
Yeah, wow.
让战斗开始吧
Let the battle begin.
对 就是这样
Yeah, there you go.
好了
There you go.
来吧 Whoo -hoo
Come on! - Whoo-hoo.
怎么啦
What?
待在里面
Stay in it.
很好 干得好
Nice, way to go.
这就对了
There you go!
来 我来付他的钱
Here, I'll pay for him.
踢得好
Nice kick!
好了 好了
There you go, there you go.
很好 把套餐给他
Nice, give him the combo.
不 婊子 切尔诺贝利
No bitch, Chernobyl.
你不能用链子
You can't use a chain.
这是什么
What is this?
裁判
Ref!
停止争吵
Stop the fight.
这是扯淡
This is bullshit.
过来 你这狗娘养的
Come here, you son of a bitch.
我可以过去吗
Can I get through, please?
不 哇
No, whoa!
哦 狗屎
Oh, shit.
这是我的孩子 伙计
That's my boy, man.
大便
Shit.
妈的 火
Shit, fire!
火 火
Fire, fire!
哦 上帝
Oh, God!
嘿
Hey.
艾比
Abby?
嗨
Hi.
谢普利 别这样
Shepley, come on.
来吧
Come on.
我和谢普利谈过了 他没事
I talked to Shepley and he's fine.
明天我会坐第一班飞机去维加斯
I'll be on the first flight to Vegas tomorrow.
嘿 只是一个想法
Hey, just a thought,
但也许你想去海市蜃楼或卢克索看看
but maybe you wanna check into the Mirage or the Luxor.
我听说他们有交易
I-I hear they have deals.
它很好
It's fine.
本尼什么也不会做
Benny's not gonna do anything.
他的骗局没有成功 没有人欠他一分钱
His scam didn't work out and no one owes him a dime.
梅 你得相信我
Mer, you just have to trust me.
再见
Bye.
我不知道我还想不想离开这张床 鸽子
I don't know if I ever wanna leave this bed, pigeon.
嘿 特拉维斯
Hey, Travis?
嗯 -你为什么叫我鸽子
Hm? - Why do you call me pigeon?
你不知道鸽子是什么吗
You don't know what a pigeon is?
是啊 一种讨厌的鸟 会往人头上拉屎
Yeah, it's an annoying bird that craps on people's heads.
不
No.
它是一只鸽子 一个迷人的女孩 一个
It's a dove, an attractive girl, a...
在扑克中获胜的一手牌
A winning hand in poker.
看到了吗
See?
你是我的鸽子
You're my pigeon.
我累坏了
I'm an exhausted pigeon.
我敢打赌
I bet.
你吗
You?
我要再睡一会儿
I'm gonna stay up for a little while.
哦
Oh.
你怕你睡觉后我又会消失吗
Are you scared I'm gonna disappear again if you go to sleep?
我突然想到了
It crossed my mind.
我爱你
I love you.
我爱你 崔维斯·马多克斯
I love you, Travis Maddox.
你爱我吗
You love me?
是纹身
It's the tattoos.
它们很酷
They're pretty cool.
你确定要这么做吗
Sure you wanna do this?
伙计 我天生就会骑马
Dude, I was born to ride.
我觉得你刚才脑损伤了
I think you got some brain damage back there.
我爱你 妈妈
I love you, Mommy.
嘿 我们农场见
Hey, I'll see you back at the ranch.
怎么啦
What?
玉米
Corn.
让我们看看这只小狗能做什么
Ah, let's see what this puppy can do.
他会没事吧
Is he gonna be okay?
Yee -ha
Yee-ha!
不
No.
我得给自己弄一个
I need to get me one of these.
哇
Whoo!
这是谁的包
Whose bag is this?
杰西
Jesse's.
杰西是谁 -我喜欢这个
Who's Jesse? - I love this thing.
没关系
Doesn't matter.
杰西有衬衫吗
Does Jesse have a shirt?
他可能
He might.
他确实有一件衬衫
He does have a shirt.
嘿
Hey.
这不是我最喜欢的风格
It's not my favorite style.
有点吵 但是
A little loud but...
他在这里也有很多钱
He also has a ton of money in here.
不 那是我的钱
Actually, no, that's my money.
你赢了
You won this?
是的
Yeah.
告诉过你我很好 -是的
Told you I'm good. - Yeah.
那么 这也是你的了
So then, this is yours too?
嗯嗯
Mm-hm.
你很有品味
You have great taste.
敬你一杯
Here's to you.
噢
Ow.
为我们干杯
Here's to us.
我的脸怎么样
How's my face?
哦
Ooh.
你看起来已经好多了
You look better already.
再去拉斯维加斯玩一晚
Vegas for another night?
那将是一场灾难
That would be a disaster.
我们开始吧
Let's do it.